marstranslation.com 2018-12-20

# Privacy | Mars Translation

Mars Translation has created the following privacy policy for our clients and our free-lance translators/gig workers in order to re-affirm our commitment to the Privacy of our partners, Clients and all other parties involved in Mars translation. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the Mars Translation site.

In order to use Mar Translation, you must read the following privacy policy statement and agree to follow all the protocols stated in the aforementioned policy. By law, all of our clients are required to follow the protocols of our privacy policy if they wish to work with us.

  1. ## Information Collected at Mars

    1. Mars Translation collects your information when you register on the Mars Translation site and when you visit Mars Translation pages. This information includes your basic personal information as well as certain financial information in case you plan on performing a transaction with Mars translation. As per the Consumer protection laws, Mars translation guarantees the absolute privacy of all of your information.
    2. Personal Information: We may collect the following types of personal information in order to provide you with the use and access to the Mars Translation site, services, and tools, and for any additional purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.
    1. ## Information Collected by Mars includes:

      1. Name, and contact information, such as email address, phone number, mobile telephone number, physical address, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information, such as bank account numbers
      2. Transactional information based on your activities on the sites (such as bidding, buying, selling, item and content you generate or that relates to your account), billing and other information you provide to purchase an item
      3. Personal information you provide to us through correspondence, chats, dispute resolution, or shared by you from other social applications, services or websites
      4. Additional personal information we ask you to submit to authenticate yourself if we believe you are violating site policies (for example, we may ask you to send us an ID to answer additional questions online to help verify your identity)
      5. Information from your interaction with our sites, services, content and advertising, including, but not limited to, device ID, device type, location, geo-location information, computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, IP address and standard web log information
      6. Aggregate Information: Mars Translation collects non-identifying, general, generic and aggregate information to better design our Website and services.
      7. Non-Personal Information: Mars Translation may collect non-personal information as you use Mars Translation. When you use the site, Mars Translation, third-party service providers (e.g. Google Analytics), and partners may receive and record non-personal information from cookies, server logs, and similar technology from your browser or mobile device, including your IP address.
      8. We may combine some Non-Personal Information with the Personal Information we collect. Where we do so, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information if the resulting combination may be used to readily identify or locate you in the same manner as Personal Information alone.
  2. ## How does Mars use your information?

    1. At MARS TRANSLATION, A 100 Percent non-disclosure policy is followed. Your information is never shared with anyone who is not related to the company or to the project at hand. That said we use your information for various parts of the processes of completing your order. Note that all these protocols exist to ensure a fast and accurate turnover. 
    2. When you use the Mars Translation site, we may request certain information. Mars Translation does not share any of your personally identifiable or transactional information with any person or entity, other than as set out in this policy. No other third party receives your personally identifiable information or other transactional data except for approximate location / geo-location information when you share that information with whom you have transactions. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our website, used to notify consumers about updates to our website and for communications, such as customer service.
    3. ### Communications:

      1. We may send you a welcome email to verify your account and other transactional emails for operational purposes, such as billing, account management, or system maintenance. You may only stop those emails by terminating your account. We may also send you promotions, product announcements, surveys, newsletters, developer updates, product evaluations, and event information or other marketing or commercial e-mails. You can opt out of receiving these email communications from Mars Translation at any time by unsubscribing using the unsubscribe link within each email, updating your e-mail preferences on your Mars Translation account or emailing us to have your contact information removed from our email list or registration database.
    4. ### Marketing:

      1. You agree that we may use your personal information to tell you about our services and tools, deliver targeted marketing and promotional offers based on your communication preferences, and customize measure and improve our advertising. You can unsubscribe from emails at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link contained in the email.
    5. ### Non-disclosure Guarantee

      1. We do not rent, sell, or share Personal Information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies for marketing purposes (including direct marketing purposes) without your permission. We may use and share Non-Personal Information for our marketing purposes, including, without limitation, marketing on other websites. For example, we may use the information to control the number of times you have seen an ad, deliver ads tailored to your interests, and measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns. You can prevent us from tailoring our ads to you on other websites by deleting your cookies (see below).
  3. ## Sharing your information

    1. We disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. As stated above, we do not disclose your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent.
    2. We may disclose personal information to our related bodies corporate and third party suppliers and service providers located overseas for some of the purposes listed above. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the overseas recipients of your personal information do not breach the privacy obligations relating to your personal information.
    3. We may disclose your personal information to entities located outside of China, including our related body’s corporates.
    4. We may share aggregate data with advertisers and other third parties. Mars Translation uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer and transaction data exchanged with our site.
  4. ## Cookies

    1. Cookies are pieces of data assigned by a web server that uniquely identify the browser on your PC. Mars Translation uses cookies called "persistent" cookies to enable the site to remember you on subsequent visits, speeding up or enhancing your experience of services or functions offered. Cookies also enable our systems to gather information about your navigational patterns through the site. You have the option to disable cookies at any time through your browsers. We may also store your website activity in cookies which may be used by third party vendors, including Google, to serve ads based on your behavior on our website.
    2. The third party vendors (e.g. Google Analytics) may receive and record non-personal information from cookies, server logs, and similar technology from your browser or mobile device, including your IP address. You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page
    3. If you access our Services with your login credentials from a social networking site (e.g., Facebook or Twitter) or if you otherwise agree to associate your Mars Translation account with a social networking account, we may receive personal information about you from such social networking site, in accordance with the terms of use and privacy policy of the social networking site. For example, Facebook may share with us your friend list, birthday, information about the interests of you or your friends or other personal information, in order to help us establish your account, tailor services to you and find other current or potential site users that you know. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via other aspects of the Site. You are also subject to the social networking site's terms of use and privacy policy. We use the (open authorization) protocol to enable us to access this information without collecting your password when you agree allow another application to access your account information.
  5. ## GDPR Compliance

Mars translation will be following the protocols of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). This means that Mars translation will provide s 200 percent guarantee that your information will not be shared will third parties,

    1. ## Cookies

      1. Cookies are pieces of data assigned by a web server that uniquely identify the browser on your PC. Mars Translation uses cookies called "persistent" cookies to enable the site to remember you on subsequent visits, speeding up or enhancing your experience of services or functions offered. Cookies also enable our systems to gather information about your navigational patterns through the site. You have the option to disable cookies at any time through your browsers. We may also store your website activity in cookies which may be used by third-party vendors, including Google, to serve ads based on your behavior on our website.
      2. The third party vendors (e.g. Google Analytics) may receive and record non-personal information from cookies, server logs, and similar technology from your browser or mobile device, including your IP address. You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page.
      3. If you access our Services with your login credentials from a social networking site (e.g., Facebook or Twitter) or if you otherwise agree to associate your Mars Translation account with a social networking account, we may receive personal information about you from such social networking site, in accordance with the terms of use and privacy policy of the social networking site. For example, Facebook may share with us your friend list, birthday, information about the interests of you or your friends or other personal information, in order to help us establish your account, tailor services to you and find other current or potential site users that you know. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via other aspects of the Site. You are also subject to the social networking site's terms of use and privacy policy. We use the (open authorization) protocol to enable us to access this information without collecting your password when you agree allow another application to access your account information.
      4. We may share aggregate data with advertisers and other third parties. Mars Translation uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer and transaction data exchanged with our site.
  6. ## Accessing your Information in compliance with GDPR

    1. ## Changing the Data

      1. To change the data, the user needs to Log In the three Mars profiles and click on the My Profile button on the drop-down menu on the top right. Once they are on the page they can press the download button on the bottom left to get their data. Likewise, if they wish to modify their data, They edit it on the My Profile page.
    2. ## GDPR Compliant Practice at Mars

      1. As of May 29, 2018, Mars Translation Pvt. Ltd are compliant with the updated General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
      2. GDPR extends the rights of clients in regards to data privacy rights concerning all of its European clients, this gives our clients a better handle on the power to control their data. Companies that provide services, and process personal data of their European clients, must comply with the set of GDPR regulations. There are specific and clear requirements that these companies must meet and basic rights that European individuals can exercise with these companies. More information about GDPR can be found in the official GDPR European Union’s website:
      3. For more information concerning the protocols of GDPR, Visit their [website](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-protection-eu_en).
      4. At Mars Translation, We have appointed a Data Protection Officer (DPO) to manage and supervise the fulfillment of all GDPR requirements, and assist any inquiries from individuals. The DPO can be reached at [support@marstranslation.com](mailto:support@marstranslation.com).
    3. ### Functions to support GDPR requirements:

      1. Mars Translation is committed to assist all their customers managing their archived data.
      2. You may also choose to permanently delete all your data.
      3. This Privacy Policy was updated on May 29, 2018
